deccanchargers.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy Policy | Official Website of Deccan Chargers IPL Team

Your privacy is of the utmost importance to DeccanChargers.com. Because we ask for some basic personal information during registration, we want you to be fully informed of how this information is gathered and used.

**Registration**

Some basic personal information is required in order to register with DeccanChargers.com –

**Email Address**

This is essential and your primary unique identifier at this site. Also, you can receive other important messages via your email account. Message board notifications, personalized newsletters, and messages sent to you by other DeccanChargers.com members rely on the email address you provide when you register.

**User Name**

This is how you are identified when you participate in forums, chats and while posting comments. While many other aspects of your account can be updated regularly, your user name cannot be changed. You do not have to provide your real name; this can be any name not yet in use at the board.

**Demographic Information**

When you register, you are asked to give demographic information (like birth year, occupation, and gender). We ask you to tell us a little about yourself so we can better understand the types of people who register. This information can also be used to provide you with content that may be of interest to you, and to show you advertisements that are relevant to your demographic information.

**Participation**

The above describes information that is provided "actively" - meaning, you choose to submit this information to us when you join DeccanChargers.com, or update your account at any point after having joined. Some other information is provided "passively" - meaning, that DeccanChargers.com obtains this information when you login to your DeccanChargers.com account and use the service.

**Public Forum**

DeccanChargers.com is a public forum and is accessible to all registered members. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in public forums becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Security**

DeccanChargers.com has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under its control. DeccanChargers.com servers have strict security in place to prevent an intruder from retrieving personal information about its users.

**Summary**

In this electronic era, when personal information can easily be obtained through various sources, DeccanChargers.com appreciates the sensitivity of any private information that you disclose to us. It is our intention to treat your account information with the highest level of care.

We may disclose members' information to our sponsors. If we are officially requested by a government or law enforcement agency, or by other agency empowered by law to access the information, we will share your information with them.
